PRELIMINARY Inventory of the Steven E. Barryte Semiconductor and computer industries: publications and documentation, ca. 1970-1999
Department of Special Collections
Steven E. Barryte Semiconductor and computer industries: publications and documentation,
ca. 1970-1999
Special Collections M1139
Barryte, Steven E., collector.
16.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Restricted access to collection. Requires 24 hours advance notice before use. Please consult Special Collections staff.
Provenance
Gift of Steven E. Barryte, 1999.
Access Terms
Computer industry.; Science--History.; Semiconductor industry.
Container List
- Advanced Micro Devices: various data books, catalogs, handbooks, product descriptions1977-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Advanced Micro Devices: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes, technical articles, and promotional product information booklets1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Advanced Micro Devices: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes, technical articles, and promotional product information booklets1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Advanced Micro Devices: various data books, catalogs, handbooks1988(cont)-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Advanced Micro Devices: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes, technical articles, and promotional product information booklets1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Advanced Micro Devices: various data books, catalogs, handbooks1990-1993 (Box 3)
- Fairchild: various data books, handbooks, product descriptions1970-1986 (Box 4)
- intel: various data books, product descriptions, manuals, and technical sheets on their processors1972-1981 (Box 5)
- intel: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- intel: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- intel: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- intel: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- intel: preliminary and final data sheets, application notes, promotional material1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Intel: various data books, manuals, and handbooks1982-1994 (Box 7)
- National Semiconductor: data books & handbooks1975-1997 (Box 8)
- National Semiconductor: reference guides and catalogs, preliminary and final datasheets, promotional materials, technical articles 1978-1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- National Semiconductor: reference guides and catalogs, preliminary and final datasheets, promotional materials1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- National Semiconductor: reference guides and catalogs, preliminary and final datasheets, promotional materials1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- National Semiconductor: reference guides and catalogs, preliminary and final datasheets, promotional materials1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- National Semiconductor: reference guides and catalogs preliminary and final datasheets, promotional materials1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Actel: FPGA Data Book and Design Guide1996 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Altera Corporation: data sheets1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AMI Semiconductors: Telecommunications and Design Manual1982 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AMI Semiconductors: MOS Product Catalog1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Array processors info, various companies: promotional & data sheets from Star Technologies, Marinco, Numerix, Analogic, Mercury Computer Systems, CSPI, Masscomp, Mars, Sky Computers, Signix, Symbolics, Floating Point Systems1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Artisan Software: product information sheets and manual1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Ashtech Inc.: product information sheets on GPS receivers1991-93 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Athena Systems: product information sheets (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Atherton Technology: product & company information, handbook1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- C-Cube Microsystems: product information sheets1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Catalyst Semiconductor, Inc: information/data sheets1989-90 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Chips and Technologies: preliminary data sheets1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Chips and Technologies: Short Form Catalog, Fall 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Chips and Technologies: Short Form Catalog1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Cirrus Logic: application notes, preliminary data sheet1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Cirrus Logic: Product Family Overview from Pixel Semicon Doctor ( a Cirrus Logic Company), Nov. 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Cisco Systems: product information sheets1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Cisco Systems: Users Newsletter, Spring1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Cybernetic MicroSystems: product information sheets & 1986 price list 1981, 1984, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- 1988(?) (Box 10, Folder 15 Cygnet Systems: promotional product information folder)
- Cypress Semiconductor: product information sheets & guides1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cypress Semiconductor: CMOS Data Book1986 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Echelon Corporation: LonWorks(tm) Product Line Brief1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- EG&G Reticon: Image Sensing Products catalog 1985(?) (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Electronic Signature Lock: patent1986 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Exar Corporation: technical product description sheets1972, 1973, 1981, 1986, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Exar Corporation: Phase-Locked Loop Data Book1978 (?) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Exar Corporation: Data book1984 (?) (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Exar Corporation: Product Guide Short Form1986 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- GEC Plessey: SOS Radiation Hard Hi-Rel IC and ASIC handbook1991 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- General Instrument: Catalog of Optoelectronic Products1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Gyration, Inc: GyroEngine data sheet1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Hewlett Packard: Quick Reference brochure1971 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: technical guides 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: Optoelectronics Designer's Catalog1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: Technical Data booklets1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: Hewlett Packard Journal, August1986 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: various data sheets1986, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: HP 6300 Optical Drive, brochure1988(?) (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: HP 75000 Product catalog, Fall/Winter1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Hewlett Packard: Software brochure1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- IAR Systems: Embedded Development Tolls Directory1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- ICS Electronics Corporation: Products brochure (Box 10, Folder 26)
- ICS Sensors: product information folder on accelerometer1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Infochip: Expanz!(tm) Micro Channer Card, product sheet1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Infochip: Expanz!(tm) Plus Data Compression Card, product sheet 1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- inmos: Databook 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Integrated Device Technology: application notes1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: CMOS Data Book1988 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: Product Selector Guide 4th qtr1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: RISC R3000 Product Info. Book1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: RISC Subsystems Prod Info book 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: R3001 RISController(tm) Performance Comparison Report 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Device Technology: Logic Data Book1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Integrated Systems Inc.: technical & promotional product info.1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Integrated Systems Inc.: newsletters1989, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Integrated Systems Inc.: Real-Time software brochure1991 (?) (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Intergraph Corporation (Advanced Processor Division): Clipper C300 Data Book 1988 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Intergraph Corporation: fact sheets, product brochures1988-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Intergraph Corporation (Advanced Processor Division): Introduction to the CLIPPER Architecture book, January 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Intersil: IM6100 CMOS 12 Bit Microprocessor Data Book1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Intersil: bulletins for the IM6100 series1978-79 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Intersil: application bulletin on data acquisition1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Intersil: Component Data Catalog1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Krysalis: two (2) Preliminary Information sheets on its product 1989 (?) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Bought by National Semiconductor
- LISP Machine Inc.: promotional product brochures for its hardware and software1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Logic Devices Incorporated: Product Catalog1986 (?) (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Logic Devices Incorporated: Application Note 1986 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Logic Devices Incorporated: three (3) product info. Booklets1988 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Logic Devices Incorporated: Fast CMOS Data Book1989 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Logic Devices Incorporated: High-Speed Register Catalog, Sept.1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- LSI Logic: product descriptions, technical sheets and manuals promotional materials, preliminary data sheets1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- LSI Logic: L64500 MIL-STD-1750A Microprocessor Technical Manual 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- LSI Logic: Digital Signal Processing (DSP) Short Form Catalog1990 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- LSI Logic: Digital Signal Processing (DSP) Short Form Catalog1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- LSI Logic: Short Form Catalog1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Lucid, Inc.: promotional "Straight talk about Lisp. Special report for the technical community"1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Lynx Real-Time Systems Inc.: product information sheets & short company publication 1988-89 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- MasPar Computer Corporation: technical articles & product Information sheets1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- MASS Microsystems: information sheet (1) on multimedia product 1991 (?) (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Maxim Integrated Products: Power Supply Circuits data book 1986 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Microbar Systems, Inc.: data/information sheets1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Micro Power Systems: product technical information1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- MIPS Computer Systems: promotional product info. folder 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Monolithic Memories: Bipolar LSI Data Book1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Monolithic Memories: 16x16 Flow-Thru(tm) Multiplier Slice data sheet1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Monolithic Memories: LSI Data Book, 7th Edition1986 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- NEC Electronics: V Series Microprocessor and DSP product descriptions, data/technical sheets and manuals, articles1984-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: Microcomputer Products Data Book 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: Linear Products Data Book1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: Microcomputer Products Data Book 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: Memory Products Data Book1989 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: Product Selection Guide1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: DSP and Speech Processor Products Data book1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: DSP and Speech Processor Products Data book1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- NEC Electronics: VR Series(tm) Microprocessors Architecture and User's Manual1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Neuron Data: promotional brochure1993 (?) (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Nitron Corp .: data sheets & booklet1973-1980 (?) (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Noren Products, Inc.: Product information sheets on cabinet cooler 1986 (?) (Box 12, Folder 4)
- NOVIX Inc.: product information sheets on its chips 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- NOVIX Inc.: "The Novix Register" bulletin, Apr.5th & July/Aug.1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Nu Thena Systems: product information folder1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Octel Communications Corporation: Aspen(tm) Voice Message System Data Sheet 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- 1991 (?) (Box 13, Folder Optivision Incorporated: promotional brochure for its OPTIPAC Image Compression)
- ParcPlace Systems Inc.: product information sheets, promotional and technical; Newsletter Summer 19881988-1991 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Performance Semiconductor Corporation: preliminary and final data sheets, product information sheets1986-1988 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- PMI (Precision Monolithics Inc.): Analog IC Data book1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Rational Software Corporation: information booklet (photocopy)1990 (?) (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Rational Software Corporation: quarterly newsletter, Spring1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Rational Software Corporation: promotional mailing1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Raytheon: Microcomputer Components data book1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Raytheon: Digital products data book1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Raytheon: Linear Integrated Circuits data book1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Raytheon: Product Selection Guide1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Raytheon: data sheets & application note on Video Product Family 1992(?) (Box 13, Folder 1)
- (Ready Systems) Hunter-Ready Systems: Real Time Applications Handbook (applications from 1983-87)1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  A company of McDonnell Douglas Corporation; Ready Systems named Hunter Ready Systems until 1987
- (Ready Systems) Hunter-Ready Systems3: promotional info.folder with data sheets and product briefs (1985-87) 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Ready Systems: product briefs & data sheets on real-time technologies1987-1990 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Reticon Corporation: product info/data sheets on Discrete Time Analog Processing1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- The Santa Cruz Operation, Inc.: promotional folder 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Saratoga Semiconductor: data sheets1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- SEQ Technologies Incorporated: Product description booklet1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SEQ Technologies Incorporated: Product Catalog1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SEQ Technologies Incorporated: Data Book1985 (?) (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SEQ Technologies Incorporated: preliminary data sheets1982-1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- SGS: Z8000 Microprocessor Family Data Book, 2nd Edition1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SGS: Shortform Semiconductor Products data book1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SGS-Thompson: Modem Databook & Applications, 1st Edition1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- SGS-Thompson & inmost: Static RAMs Databook, 1st Edition1989 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Sherpa Corporation: corporate & product information sheets, data sheets, User Brief1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Signetics Corporation: data sheets1970, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Signetics Corporation: bit-slice technologies- programming and applications manuals, data sheets, articles, and product guides 1976-1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Signetics Corporation: Logic, Memories, Interface, Analog, Microprocessor, Military Data Manual1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Signetics Corporation: Analog Data Manual 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: MOS Microprocessor Data Manual 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Integrated Fuse Logic Data Manual1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Linear LSI Europaproducts Data Manual1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Linear LSI Full Product Guide1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: TTL Data Manual 1984 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Bipolar LSI Data Manual1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: product/data information sheets1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Bipolar Memory Data manual1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Programmable Logic Data Manual1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: High-Speed CMOS Data Manual1986 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: SMD pocket guide1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Fiber Optic Communication Data and Applications1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Military Product Reference Guide1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: 80C51 and Derivative Microcontrollers Data Handbook1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Signetics Corporation: Master Product Catalog1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Sierra Semiconductor Corporation: data and prod. info sheet 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Silicon Composers Inc.: product/data information sheets1988-89 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Siliconix incorporated: Analog Switches & Their Applications, Jun. 1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Siliconix incorporated: LSI Data book Design Catalog, July1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Siliconix incorporated: Analog Switch & IC product data book, Jan. 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Siliconix incorporated: MOSPOWER Applications Handbook1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Siliconix incorporated: Integrated Circuits Data Book, March 1985 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Software Components Group: product information sheets, including a comparative study of pSOS vs. VRTX1985-1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Software Components Group: Psos-68K & pROBE-68 Evaluation Package User's Guide1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Software Components Group: promotional folder1986 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Software Components Group: How To Develop Bullet-Proof Real-Time Systems, September 1990 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Stanford Telecommunications, Inc.: product information/data sheets1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Stanford Telecommunications, Inc.: Custom Products Short Form Catalog1988 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Sun Microelectronics: Some Hard Questions about Java Chips, Q&A booklet from their marketing division1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Sun Microsystems: technical overviews and product info booklets 1983-1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Supertex, Inc.: data sheet for programmable encoder/decoder1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Synertek, Inc.: Data Book1983 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Systolic Systems Incorporated: product information sheets 1983, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- TeamOne Systems, Inc.: informational/promotional folder1990 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Teledyne Semiconductor: Data Acquisition Design Handbook1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Titan Corporation: Titan/ Severe Environment Systems (SESCO) SEC 80 computer products information sheets 1986 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- SESCO: Militarized Microcomputers product guide1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- TRW LSI Products Inc: Catalog 811981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- TRW LSI Products Inc: preliminary & final data sheets, application notes, technical articles promotional product information booklets1977-1992 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Ungermann-Bass, Inc.: one (1) product information sheet1987 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Verity, Inc.: TOPIC(r) Retrieval System information sheets and promotional brochure1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- ViCOM Visual Computing: News release, corporate info and a product information brochure1991 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- ViewStar Corporation: promotional folder1988-9 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Vitelic Corporation: Memory Data Catalog1990-91 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- VLSI Technology, Inc.: preliminary data sheets & booklets 1987, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- VLSI Technology, Inc.: Quick Reference Guide to Logic products1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- VLSI Technology, Inc.: Short Form Catalog, March1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- VLSI Technology, Inc.: Short Form Catalog, May1991 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- VLSI Technology, Inc.: Products Overview 32-bit ARM/RISC processor family, January 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- WSI (Waferscale Integration, Inc.): promotional article, product selector guide, preliminary & final data sheets, application notes1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- WSI (Waferscale Integration, Inc.): High Performance CMOS1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Weitek Corporation: Preliminary and Advanced Data sheets, product summaries, short form catalog1982 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Western Digital Corporation: Product guide, data sheets, promotional product information sheets1975-1987 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- WindRiver Systems: product information folder1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- WindRiver Systems: winworld newsletter, June1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- WindRiver Systems: company and product info. Brochure1997 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Xicor, Inc.: Data sheets 1980-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Xicor, Inc.: Data sheets and Reference Guide to Xicor Nonvolatile Memories1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Xicor, Inc.: Data Book1985 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Zilog, Inc.: Z8 family: product descriptions & specifications application notes, data sheets 1979-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Z80 family: product descriptions & specifications handbook, application notes, data sheets, programmers' reference guides, technical articles1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Z800 family: preliminary product specification application notes, data sheets, technical articles1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Z800 family: product descriptions & specifications handbook, application notes, data sheets, programmers' reference guides, technical articles1977-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: product descriptions & specifications, promotional brochures application notes, data sheets (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Data Book1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Peripherals: Technical Overview1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Z8000 CPU Technical Manual, January1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Microprocessor Applications Reference Book, Volume 2, August 1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Software Directory, Winter1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Component Products Profile1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Components Data Book1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Components Shortform1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Components Shortform1988 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Components Shortform1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Zilog, Inc.: Shortform Catalog1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- ZORAN Corporation: Digital Signal Processors Data Book1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ZORAN Corporation: ZR34325 32-bit Floating Point Vector Signal Processor Engineering Data book, May 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ZORAN Corporation: Product Guide, October 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ZORAN Corporation: ZR34325 Application Development Tools1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ZORAN Corporation: preliminary data sheet, January 1994 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- ZyMOS Corporation: preliminary data sheets, applications notes promotional booklets & news release1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)